Simon Flexner Papers 1891-1946 Mss.B.F365
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Simon Flexner Papers, 1891-1946; 115.5 linear feet
  - Kelly, Harris
  - Kelly, Howard A.
  - Kelly, J. B.
  - Kelly, J. P.
  - Kelly, Madaline E.
  - Kelly, Olga
  - Kelly, Robert L.
  - Kelly, William E.
  - Kelsey, Carl
  - Kelter, Minnie
  - Kelton, Walter
  - Kemp, James P.
  - Kemp, John
  - Kemper, Sallie Underhill
  - Kemple, Frederick C
  - Kempner, Walter
  - Kempter, J. E.
  - Kendall, Ada
  - Kendall, Arthur I.
  - Kendall, Christine Herter
  - Kendall, Edward C.
  - Kendall, James
  - Kendall, William
  - Kendrick, John F.
  - Kennady, Paul
  - Kennard, Edward M.
  - Kennedy, Ellen
  - Kennedy, Foster
  - Kennedy, James M.
  - Kennedy, John B.
  - Kennedy, Mary A.
  - Kennedy, Nellie
  - Kennedy, R. M.
  - Kennedy, Robert H.
  - Kennedy and Co.
  - Kenner, Marcus L.
  - Kenney, John A.
  - Kenney, John F.
  - Kennisoh, Samuel I.
  - Kenny, Mr.
  - Kenny, E. C.
  - Kenny, K.
  - Kent, Fred S.
  - Kent, George H.
  - Kent, Henry W.
  - Kent, J. Bryden
  - Kent, R. A.
  - Kentuckians, The
  - Kentucky Pioneer Memorial
  - Kenyon, Josephine Hemenway
  - Kenzel, Madeltine V.
  - Keogh, Alfred
  - Keppel, Frederick D.
  - Keppel, Frederick P.
  - Ker, Claude B.
  - Kerbosch, M.
  - Kerkhof, Dr.
  - Kerley, Charles G.
  - Kernan, W. E.
  - Kernodle, G. W.
  - Kerr, A. C.
  - Kerr, J. P.
  - Kerr, John W.
  - Kerr, W. A. R.
  - Kertesz, Geza
  - Keschner, Moses
  - Kesler, Rachel Hoyle
  - Kessel, John F.
  - Kestner, O.
  - Kettenring, Alfred William
  - Key, Cyrilla
  - Keyes, Edward L., Jr.
  - Keyes, Frederick G.
  - Keyes, Preston
  - Keyser, Linwood D.
  - Keyser, R. Brent
  - Keysser
  - Keystone View Co.
  - Khan, Zorab Ameer
  - Kibrick, Andre C.
  - Kidder, A. V.
  - Kiel, O. B.
  - Kiep, O. C.
  - Kierulff, L. A.
  - Kikuth, Walter
  - Kilduffe, Robert A.
  - Kilgore, A. R.
  - Kille, Willard B.
  - Killian, Miss
  - Killion, T. S.
  - Kimball, Alfred R.
  - Kimball, Arthur R.
  - Kimball, Reuel B.
  - Kimberlin, A. C.
  - Kimura, Hideo
  - Kimura, N.
  - Kimura, Onari
  - Kimura, Ren
  - Kin, Yamei
  - Kindell, F. B.
  - Kindleberger, C. P.
  - King, Beth
  - King, C. P.
  - King, C. W.
  - King, Carlos T.
  - King, Charles T.
  - King, D. MacDougall
  - King, David Bennett
  - King, Ernestine M.
  - King, George Clifford
  - King, George W.
  - King, H. H.
  - King, H. Y.
  - King, Hortense
  - King, James E.
  - King, Jeannette Moore
  - King, John T., Jr.
  - King, Kimgpah T.
  - King, Parks M.
  - King, Robert W.
  - King, Sibyl
  - King, W. L. Mackenzie
  - King, Wyncie
  - Kinghorn, Hugh M.
  - Kingsbury, John Adams, 4 folders
  - Kingsley, C.
  - Kinley, David
  - Kinloch, I. P.
  - Kinney, C. W.
  - Kinney, DeLan
  - Kinnicutt, Roger
  - Kinsella, Ralph A.
  - Kipper, H. B.
  - Kipps Bay Neighborhood
  - Kirby, Darwin
  - Kirby, George H.
  - Kirbysmith, R. M.
  - Kirchner, Otto
  - Kirk, Dr.
  - Kirk, Arthur A.
  - Kirk, Edward C.
  - Kirk, Edwin G.
  - Kirk, George
  - Kirk, Robert H.
  - Kirk, Sophia
  - Kirkbride, Franklin B.
  - Kirkbride, Mary Butler, 2 folders
  - Kirkland, J. H.
  - Kirkpatrick, Rebecca E.
  - Kirkwood, Marie
  - Kirman, David
  - Kirsch, Anselm B.
  - Kirschbaum, W.
  - Kirshborg, J. S.
  - Kisher, S. I.
  - Kissel, Frances Dallett
  - Kisskalt, Karl
  - Kitasato, Shibasaburo, 1915-1931; 15 items
  - Kitashima, Taichi
  - Kitchen, Thurman D.
  - Kitto, Robert Andrew
  - Kittrell, Thomas F.
  - Kiyono, K.
  - Klaas, Max
  - Klatery, Joseph O.
  - Klauber, Adolph
  - Klauber, Anna
  - Klauber, Edward
  - Klauber, Fanny
  - Klausz, Mrs. John
  - Klebs, Arnold C.
  - Kleeman, R. D.
  - Klein, A. W.
  - Klein, John C.
  - Klein, Pauline von
  - Klein, Philip
  - Klein, Robert J.
  - Klein, S. R.
  - Klein, Sander Paul
  - Klein, Stanilaus
  - Klein, Thomas
  - Kleinberg, Samuel
  - Kleine, F. K.
  - Kleiner, Israel Simon, 1914-1934; 50 items
    Includes: General administrative correspondence. Note to SF about his appointment to professorship of physiological chemistry at New York Homeopathic Medical College, 8/4/19. Letter about his application for chair at University of Pennsylvania vacated by Alonzo Taylor, 1922.
  - Klieneberger, Emy
  - Kligler, I. J., 3 folders
  - Kliman, F .E.
  - Kline, Dr.
  - Kline, Benjamin S.
  - Kline, Julia W.
  - Kling, Carl A.
  - Klopp, Henry I.
  - Klosterman, Julius
  - Klotz, Oskar
  - Klotz, Walter C.
  - Klugh, George F.
  - Knap and Mason
  - Knapp, Albert
  - Knapp, Arnold
  - Knapp, Robert P.
  - Knassl-Lenz, E.
  - Knauth, Mrs. Oswald
  - Knecht, Mercel
  - Knibbs, G. H.
  - Knickerbocker Hospital
  - Knight, H. Fuller
  - Knipfer, Paul
  - Knipp, John C. and Sons
  - Kno, P. W.
  - Knobel, Gratia Esher
  - Knoblauch, Charles E.
  - Knoblock, Marie
  - Knoeppel, Raymond J.
  - Knofflock, Julia F.
  - Knoll, Otto
  - Knoop, Franz G., 1912-1927; 6 items
  - Knopf, Alfred A.
  - Knopf, Gigard Adolphus, 1914-1939; 40 items
    Includes: Letter to SF appealing for funds for his tuberculosis research at New York Post-Graduate Medical School, 3/23/14. General correspondence.
  - Knopf, S. Adolphus
  - Knowles, J. W.
  - Knowlton, Millard
  - Knowlton, R. H.
  - Knox, J. H. Mason, Jr.
  - Knudsen, Martin
  - Knutti, Ralph E.
  - Koangting, L.
  - Kobayashi, R.
  - Kobayashi, Sakae
  - Kobelt, Nina
  - Kober, George Martin, 1912-1930; 2 folders
    Includes: Administrative correspondence about Association of American Physicians.
  - Kober, Philip Adolph
  - Kober Drug and Chemical Co.
  - Koch, Edward W.
  - Koch, Joseph
  - Koch, Robert
  - Kocousky, P.
  - Kodama, N. H.
  - Koechk, Victor, and Co.
  - Koefod, H. O.
  - Koenig, N. E.
  - Excerpts from "Hermann von Hemhottz"
  - Koessler, Karl K.
  - Kofoid, Charles A.
  - Koga, Gensabura
  - Kohlbry, Carl O.
  - Kohler, Arnold
  - Kohler, Elmer Peter, 1921-1933; 40 items
    Includes: Correspondence about openings in chemistry at RIMR, 1923 and 1926. Correspondence concerning address by Max Bergmann at RIMR, 1933.
  - Kohman, Edward F.
  - Kohn, Hans
  - Kohn, Henry H.
  - Kohut, Rebekah
  - Kolb, J. Leo
  - Kolle, W.
  - Kolmer, John A.
  - Kolodny, Anatol
  - Komatsu, Shigeru
  - Kominz, J. S.
  - Komora, Paul O.
  - Kondo, Shiji
  - Konenkov, Sergei T.
  - Konenkov, Mrs. Sergei T.
  - Koo, U. R. Wellington
  - Kopaczewski, W.
  - Kepeloff, Nicholas
  - Kopetsky, Roscoe C.
  - Koplik, Henry
  - Koplik, Rosalie
  - Koppanyi, Theodor
  - Koppenhauer, Lulu M.
  - Koranyi, Alexander von
  - Korb, Charles
  - Korenchevsky, Vladimir
  - Kornhauser, S. I.
  - Kornreich, C. P.
  - Korns, John H.
  - Korosy, Francis von
  - Korosy, Kornel von
  - Koser, Stewart A.
  - Kosmak, George W.
  - Kossell, Albrecht, 1912-1927; 20 items
    Includes: Recommendation of Professor Conheim to SF. General correspondence.
  - Kotsovsky, D.
  - Kottwitz, Robert A.
  - Kovacs, Nikolaus
  - Koves, Dezso
  - Kozelka, Dr.
  - Kracke, Roy R.
  - Kraemer, Henry
  - Kraepelin, Emil
  - Krahforst, L. R.
  - Kraines, S. H.
  - Krajewski, Eugene
  - Kraker, Dorothy Rogers
  - Kramer, David
  - Kramer, G. B.
  - Kramer, Herman
  - Kramer, James G.
  - Kramer, S. D.
  - Kramer, S. David
  - Kramer, S. P.
  - Kraus, Anton F.
  - Kraus, Charles A.
  - Kraus, E. J.
  - Kraus, Fr
  - Kraus, Geheimrat
  - Kraus, Louis, Jr.
  - Kraus, Rodolpho, 2 folders
  - Kraus, Walter M.
  - Krause, A. C.
  - Krause, Allen K.
  - Krause, M.
  - Krause, Paul
  - Krauskopf, Joseph
  - Krauspe, Case
  - Krauss, Maurice D.
  - Krebs, Dr. Carl
  - Kredell, Frederick E.
  - Krehbiel, H. E.
  - Krehl, M. Ludolf
  - Kreider, George N.
  - Kremers, Edward D.
  - Kress, George H.
  - Kretschmer, Herman L.
  - Kretschmer, Paul
  - Kretz, Johannes
  - Kretz, Marie
  - Krieg, Wallace and McQuaide
  - Krieghbaum, Hillier
  - Kritschewsky, J. L.
  - Kritschewsky, Rofess I.
  - Kritz, Joseph R.
  - Kroeh, Karl F.
  - Krogness, C. George, Jr.
  - Kroll, Ernest
  - Kroos, H.
  - Kropp, George
  - Kroupa, Mildred
  - Krueger, Albert P.
  - Krueger, J. W.
  - Krug, Otto
  - Kruholz, Sigmund
  - Krumbhaar, Edward B.
  - Krumrein, Louis F.
  - Krumwiede, Charles
  - Kubie, Lawrence S.
  - Kuczynski, Max H.
  - Kudner, Dan F.
  - Kudo, R.
  - Kudd, Taku Zasu
  - Kugelmass, I. Newton
  - Kuhns, C. C.
  - Kulp, Matilda G.
  - Kumagai, Taizo
  - Kumpf, J. E.
  - Kunitz, Moses
  - Kunkel, Louis O.
  - Kuntz, C. E.
  - Kunz, George F.
  - Kunze, Edward J.
  - Kurokawa, A.
  - Kurtz, Arthur D.
  - Kuryihski (?)
  - Kushner, David H.
  - Kuttner, Ann Gaylor
  - Kyaw, Dr.
  - Kyes, Preston
  - Laboratory
  - Laboratory Equipment Co.
  - Laboratory Notes: Miscellany, 1912-1931; 3 folders
    Includes: Miscellaneous laboratory notes on 5x8 index cards.
  - Laboratory Theatre
  - Labry, A. St. John
  - Lacy, George R.
  - Lacy, Mrs. W. A.
  - Ladd, William
  - Ladd, William S.
  - Ladd-Franklin, Mrs. C.
  - Ladeuze, P.
  - Ladew, J. Harvey
  - Laemmle, Carl
  - La Farge, Florence Bayard
  - La Fetra, Linnaeus E.
  - La Fleur Florence A.
  - Laffont, A.
  - La Fore, Edward
  - Lagerson, Victor B.
  - La Grinder, R. A.
  - La Guardia, Fiorello H.
  - Lahrheim, J.
  - Laidlaw, James L.
  - Laidlaw, P. P.
  - Laik, David
  - Lain Everett S.
  - Laird, Elizabeth R.
  - Laird, John L.
  - Lakatos, Victor
  - Lake, Kathleen
  - Lakeman, Curtis E.
  - Lal, R. B.
  - Lamar, A. L.
  - Lamar, Richard V.
  - Lamb, Brockenbrough
  - Lamb, Dorothy N.
  - Lamb, Robert Scott
  - Lambert, Alexander
  - Lambert, Robert A.
  - Lambert, Robert K.
  - Lambert, Samuel W.
  - Lambie, Joseph T.
  - Lamm, Stanley S.
  - Lamo, F. Martinez
  - Lamont, Florence
  - Lamont, Thomas W.
  - La Motte Chemical Products Co.
  - Lamson, R. W.
  - Lamy, Maurice
  - Lancaster Press, Inc.
  - Lancefield, Mrs. D. E.
  - Lancefield, Rebecca C.
  - Lancet, The
  - Landau, Edmund
  - Landau, Marianne Ehrlich
  - Landauer, Bella C.
  - Landauer, Walter
  - Landis, H. R. M.
  - Landis, John H.
  - Landman, Hattie
  - Landouzy, L.
  - Landsberg, Mrs. Eric
  - Landsberger, John A.
  - Landsman, I. J.
  - Landsteiner, Helene
  - Landsteiner, Karl, 4 folders
    Includes: Administrative correspondence.
    - Folder 1, 1914-1924
    - Folder 2, 1925-1929
    - Folder 3, 1930-1937
    - Memoir by S. Flexner
  - Lane, Franklin K.
  - Lane, Gertrude B.
  - Lane, J. F.
  - Lane, John E.
  - Lane, Laura A.
  - Lane, M.
  - Lane, R. A.
  - Lane, W. Arbuthnot
  - Lane, Winifred H.
  - Lang, Mrs. C.
  - Lang, Herbert
  - Lange, Bruno
  - Lange, Fritz
  - Langelaan, J. W.
  - Langenbeck, Clara
  - Langfeld, Millard
  - Langing, Victor P.
  - Langley, Alison
  - Langley, Mrs. J. N.
  - Langston, Wann
  - Langworthy, Orthello R.
  - Langworthy, Virginia
  - Lanier, Henry W.
  - Lansdale, Philip M.
  - Lansdown, Frances Shaw
  - Lansing, Robert
  - Lantry, John
  - Lanza, A. J.
  - La Pierre, L. F.
  - Lapowski, B.
  - Lapp, Nathan
  - Lappin, R.
  - Laqueur, Ernst
  - Larde, Dr.
  - Larimore, Louise D.
  - Larkey, Sanford V.
  - Larkin, John H.
  - Larkins, F. M.
  - Larner, Herbert B.
  - Larson, M. Burneice
  - Larson, W. P.
  - La Rue, Wayne Spence
  - Lasareff, Prof.
  - Lascelles, Norman C.
  - Lasnitzki, Arthur
  - Lassman, Guenther W.
  - Latcher, Buel
  - Latham, Ada H.
  - Latham, V. A.
  - Lathrop, Abbie E. C.
  - Lathrop, Carl O.
  - Lathrop, M. E.
  - Lattimore, Eleanor Larrabee
  - Laualle, Robertson
  - Laubaugh, Dr.
  - Lauck, R. C.
  - Laue, Prof.
  - Lauer, Mosella
  - Laughlin, Harry H.
  - Laughlin, N. W. M.
  - Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial
  - Laurel-in-the-Pines
  - Laurencena, Ignacio Martinez
  - Lauriat, Charles E., Co.
  - Lautenbach, B. B.
  - Lautenschlager, F. and M.
  - Laveran, A.
  - Lavin, George F.
  - Lavinder, C. H.
  - Lavoisier portrait
  - Law, Y. L.
  - Lawall, Charles H.
  - Lawes Agricultural Trust
  - Lawler, Elsie M.
  - Lawrence, F. B.
  - Lawrence, Joseph S.
  - Lawrence, Virginia
  - Lawson, Mary Rowley, 2 folders
    - Folder 1, 1911-1919
    - Folder 2, 1920
  - Lawyers Club
  - Lay, George C.
  - Lazare Agency, Inc.
  - Lazarus-Barlow, W. S.
  - Lazell, Edward W.
  - Lea, Charles M.
  - Lea, Georgia C
  - Lea, W. L.
  - Lea and Febiger, Publishers
  - Leach, Charles N.
    - Folder, 1937; 3 items
    - "Comparative Methods of Diagnosis of Rabies in Animals"
  - Leach, E.
  - Leach, Henry Goddard
  - Leach, J. Ray
  - Leadingham, R. W.
  - League of All Jewish Institutions
  - League of Nations, 1922; 2 folders
    Includes: Minutes of Second Conference on Standardization of Serums and Biological Reactions, Paris, 1922.
  - League of Nations Association
  - League of Nations, Health Officers
  - League of Nations Institute of Intellectual Cooperation
  - League of Nations Non-Partisan Association, Inc.
  - Leake, Chauncey D.
  - Leake, James P.
  - Leal, Augusto
  - Lean, Alice R.
  - Leao and Cox
  - Leaper, Warren E.
  - Learned, William S.
  - Leary, Major
  - Leary, Montgomery E.
  - Leary, Timothy
  - Leary's Book Store
  - Leask, Margaret
  - Leathers, W. S.
  - Leathes, J. B.
  - Leavitt, Charles Wellford
  - LeBeau, L. P.
  - LeBlanc, D. J.
  - LeBlanc, Thomas J.
  - Lebre, Victor N.
  - Lecointe, G.
  - Lecomte, du Nouy, Pierre
  - Lecount, E. R.
  - Ledbetter, R. E.
  - Leddy, Percy A.
  - Lederle, Ernst J.
  - Lederle Laboratory
  - Ledingham, John C. G., 1914, 1927-1934; 32 items
  - Ledoux, Urbain
  - Lee, A. G.
  - Lee, Burton James
  - Lee, Elmer
  - Lee, Esther W.
  - Lee, Ferdinand C.
  - Lee, Frederic Schiller, 2 folders
    Includes: Correspondence on his lecture to Harvey Society, 1913. Correspondence about antivivisectionists. Correspondence on nominations of Richard Pearce and Francis Peyton Rous to Century Club. Administrative letters on International Physiological Congress, 1929.
    - Folder 1, 1916-1917
    - Folder 1, 1918-1929
  - Lee, George R.
  - Lee, Ivy Ledbetter, 7 folders
    Includes: Correspondence on press releases of RIMR.
    - Folder 1, 1914-1916
    - Folder 2, 1917-1918
    - Folder 3, 1919-1920
    - Folder 4, 1921-1923
    - Folder 5, 1924-1927
    - Folder 6, 1928-1929
    - Folder 7, 1930-1934
  - Lee, J. W., Jr.
  - Lee, Jan van der
  - Lee, Jeanette
  - Lee, Roger I.
  - Lee, Russel van Arsdale
  - Lee, Viscount of Fareham
  - Lee, Walter W.
  - Lee, Y. S.
  - Lee Hospital
  - Leech, J. W.
  - Lees, H. D.
  - Leete, F. D.
  - Leeuwen, W. Storm van
  - Lefschetz, Solomon
  - Legg, Arthur T.
  - Leggett, Florence
  - Legnani, Ugo
  - Legrand, Isidore
  - LeGuyon, Dr.
  - Lehigh Valley Medical Association
  - Lehing, William G.
  - Lehman, Alvin
  - Lehman, Herbert H.
  - Lehman, Irving
  - Lehmann, J. F.
  - Lehmann, Walter
  - Lehrfeld, Louis
  - Leidesdorf, Samuel D.
  - Leifson, Einar
  - Leight, Rose
  - Leiner, Carl
  - Leishman, William B.
  - Leitch, Archibald
  - Leith, R. F. C.
  - Leitz, Ernst
  - Leland, Waldo G.
  - Lemaitre, Victor
  - Lemann, Isaac Ivan
  - LeMee, J. M.
  - Lemel, Samuel L.
  - Lemke, Leo
  - LeMoignic, Dr.
  - Lemon, Harvey B.
  - Lenci, Pedro
  - Lenier, Joshua H.
  - Lennette, Edwin H.
  - Lennox, William G.
  - Lenroot, Katharine F.
  - Lenschner, Ida D.
  - Lent, W. F.
  - Lente, Ellen K.
  - Lentz, Otto
  - Lentz, Wolf
  - Leo, S. Newton
  - Leonard, Oscar
  - Leonard, Veader
  - Leonard, Walter A.
  - Leopold, Samuel
  - Lepine, Jean
  - Leredde, M.
  - LeRoy, Bernard R.
  - Lesage, A.
  - Lesage, Jean
  - Lescarboura, Austin C.
  - Leschke, Erich
  - Lescohier, A. W.
  - Leslie, Arthur
  - Leslie, E.
  - Leslie's Weekly
  - Lessa, Gustavo
  - Lesser, Ernst J.
  - Lesser, F. L.
  - Lesser, Sol
  - Lester, Lora Elderkin
  - Lester, Richard M.
  - Leszynsky, William M.
  - Letterman General Hospital
  - Leubner, Mrs. R.
  - Leupp, Constance D.
  - Leuschner, A. O.
  - Levaditi, C.
  - Levaditi, D.
  - Levaditi, M.
  - Levanger, Eugenia Dudley
  - Levene, Ann
  - Levene, Phoebus Aaron Theodore, 10 folders
    Includes: Administrative correspondence about his laboratory at RIMR. Letter to SF about Casimir Funk's return to work with vitamins, especially chemistry of antiberiberi vitainine, 2/16/20. Letter from SF to Levene on latter's chemotherapy research, and SF's opinion of Jacobs' research, 3/17/21. Copy of letter from Levene about future organization of chemotherapy research at RIMR. Letter from SF about decision of W. J. V. Osterhout to work at RIMR, 10/7/24. Reports of work done in Levene's laboratory, 1925. Letter to SF discussing Jacobs' work and need for persons acquainted with methods of microanalysis, 8/8/25. Letter to SF on work of Baudisch in photochemistry of pyrimidines, 11/23/25. Letter to SF expressing his opinions of work of Bancroft and Rutzler's and Anson and Mirsky's on the reversibility of protein denaturation, 6/10/31. Letter to SF.explaining he could soon describe in detail pattern of nucleic acid molecules, and outlining work in the physical analysis of these substances in photochemical reactions, 7/1?/33. Letter to SF about place of Max Bergmann among contemporary chemists with leanings towards biology, including an expression of views on new trends in biochemistry and those interested in biologically active substances, 11/11/33. Letter to SF (not sent) offering to relinquish work on proteins and carbohydrates to accommodate Bergmann, 11/13/33. Correspondence about Bergmann's arrival at RIMR, 1934. Personal correspondence with SF in England, 1937-1938. Address given by SF at Levene's funeral 9/9/40.
    - Folder 1, 1910-1919
    - Folder 2, 1920-1921
    - Folder 3, 1922-1923
    - Folder 4, 1924-1925
    - Folder 5, 1926-1927
    - Folder 6, 1928-1929
    - Folder 7, 1930-1931
    - Folder 8, 1932-1933
    - Folder 9, 1934-1935
    - Folder 10, 1936-1940
  - Leventritt, David
  - Levi, Eltore
  - Levi, Giuseppe
  - Levien, Jacques
  - Levien, Morris Flexner
  - Levin, Charles A.
  - Levin, Isaac
  - Levin, Oscar L.
  - Levin, S.
  - Levine, B. S.
  - Levine, Benjamin J.
  - Levine, Lester M.
  - Levine, Max
  - Levine, Michael
  - Levine, Philip
  - Levine, S. A.
  - Levine, Samuel A.
  - Levinson, Sidney O.
  - Levinthal, Walter
  - Levit, S. G.
  - Levitas, George M.
  - Levy, A. F.
  - Levy, Ernst
  - Levy, Eva Garson
  - Levy, Irma B.
  - Levy, Julius
  - Levy, Marthe
  - Levy, Robert L.
  - LeWald, L. T.
  - Lewengood, Jacob
  - Lewi, Maurice J.
  - Lewi, William Grant
  - Lewin, Carl
  - Lewin, Philip
  - Lewin, Samuel
  - Lewinski-Corwin, E. H.
  - Lewinson, Jean
  - Lewis, C. T.
  - Lewis, D. M.
  - Lewis, Dean
  - Lewis, E. T.
  - Lewis, Edward M.
  - Lewis, Elizabeth Price
  - Lewis, F. Park
  - Lewis, Gilbert N.
  - Lewis, H. Edwin
  - Lewis, Harry S.
  - Lewis, Jacques M.
  - Lewis, Juan F.
  - Lewis, Julius H.
  - Lewis, Louise D.
  - Lewis, Malcolm
  - Lewis, Margaret Reed
  - Lewis, Morris J.
  - Lewis, P. M.
  - Lewis, Paul A., 4 folders
    - Folder 1, 1913-1917
    - Folder 2, 1918-1922
    - Folder 3, 1923-1925
    - Folder 4, 1926-1929
  - Lewis, Robert
  - Lewis, Sherley
  - Lewis, Thomas
  - Lewis, W. S.
  - Lewisohn, Adolph
  - Lewisohn, Richard
  - Lewy, F. H.
  - Leyden, Dorothy Graham
  - Leza, Francisco
  - L'Hermitte, Jean
  - Li, P. M.
  - Libermann, Dr.
  - Liberty Music Shops
  - Liberty Mutual Insurance Co.
  - Libman, A. L.
  - Libman, Emanuel
  - Library Bureau
  - Library Company of Phila.
  - Library of Congress
  - Library, Rockefeller Foundation
  - Licht, William H.
  - Lichten, Grace M.
  - Lichtman, S. S.
  - Lichtmann, Sina
  - Lichtwitz, L.
  - Lieb, Charles C.
  - Lieb, Clarence William
  - Lieb, John W.
  - Lieber, Hugo
  - Lieberman, Shulamite Ben-Hasel
  - Liebermann, Leo von Szent-Lorinez
  - Liebermann, Paul
  - Liebermann, Theresa de
  - Lieberson, Frank
  - Lief, Harold
  - Life Magazine
  - Lifshutz, N.
  - Light, A. L.
  - Lightfoot, Gerald
  - Lilien, Adolph
  - Lilienthal, Howard
  - Lillard, R. W.
  - Lillie, Frank Rattray, 2 folders
    Includes: Correspondence about SF's lectures at Marine Biological Laboratory, Woods Hole, summers 1915-1938. Letter to SF on plans for new laboratory of biochemistry and biophysics at Marine Biological Laboratory, 3/19/21. List of investigators of Marine Biological Laboratory, summer 1923. Letters on appeal to Rockefeller Foundation for funding of research into "vital process" or "experimental biology," 1934. Correspondence about National Academy of Sciences Standing Committee on Funds for Academy Purposes, 1935. Correspondence about nominations to Science Advisory Committee (later, Science Advisory Board) by President Roosevelt, 1935. List of members of the Committee, 1935. Correspondence concerning National Research Council Fellowship Board in Physics, Chemistry, Mathematics and Biology funds to be received from Rockefeller Foundation, 1937-40. Minutes of Advisory Committee on fellowships of National Research Council, 1/11/36.
    - Folder 1, 1915-1927
    - Folder 2, 1928-1938
  - Lillie, Ralph S.
  - Lilly, Miss Gregory
  - Lilly, Katharine
  - Lillyman, Clara
  - Lim, E. S.
  - Lim, Robert K. S.
  - Lima, A. da Costa
  - Limousin, H.
  - Limper, Maragret A.
  - Lincoln, Philma
  - Lincoln School
  - Lincoln University
  - Lind, Mr.
  - Lind, A.
  - Lind, Medora
  - Lind, S. C.
  - Lindbergh, Charles A.
  - Linden, Maria Grafin von
  - Lindenbaum, Rosa Kleiner
  - Lindenberg, A.
  - Lineberger, Walter F.
  - Lindenmeyr
  - Linder, Geoffry C.
  - Lindner, K.
  - Lindquist, Oscar
  - Lindsay, Alexander Dunlop
  - Lindsay, Janvier W.
  - Lindsey, E.
  - Lindsley, William B.
  - Lingamfelter, Sarah S.
  - Linhart, G. A.
  - Linhart, L. B.
  - Link, J. A.
  - Linkey, Mrs. Julius
  - Linn, Mrs.
  - Linn, Charles Clark
  - Lintz, William
  - Lionberger, Isaac H.
  - Lipman, Jacob G.
  - Lipmann, Fritz
  - Lipmann, Walter
  - Lippingott, Leon S.
  - Lippmann, Walter
  - Lipschutz, Dr. B.
  - Lioschutz, Harold
  - Lisor, G. M.
  - Lister, F. S.
  - Lister, Roy
  - Lister, Spencer
  - Lister Institute
  - Lists
  - Lit, Jamie Reed
  - Little, A. D.
  - Little, Clarence C.
  - Little, David M., Jr.
  - Little, Dorothy R.
  - Little, Ralph B.
  - Little, Robert Parker
  - Little Sisters of the Poor
  - Littlefield, C. O.
  - Littlejohn, R. P.
  - Liu, J. Heng
  - Liveright, Otto K.
  - Liverpool School of Tropical Medicine
  - Livingston, Bernard
  - Livingston, Burton Edward, 1919-1930; 5 folders
    Includes: Letter of Livingston to James M. Cattell (copy) accepting secretaryship of AAAS, 1920. Administrative correspondence, minutes of Executive Council, semiannual reports of secretary of AAAS, 1921-1924.
  - Livingstone, Colin H.
  - Lloyd, A. S.
  - Lloyd, Dorothy J.
  - Lloyd, F. E.
  - Lloyd, Gerrit
  - Lloyd, James Hendrie
  - Lloyd, Richard W.
  - Lloyd, Samuel
  - Lloyd-Smith, Wilton
  - Lobel, Sophie
  - Lobenstine, Edwin C.
  - Locke, Edwin A.
  - Locket, Hersey G.
  - Lockett, Everett A.
  - Lockie, Alice N.
  - Lockhart, Henry Jr.
  - Lockhart, Robert
  - Lockie, Alice
  - Lockwood, Elizabeth A.
  - Lockwood, Ferris C.
  - Lockwood, William A.
  - Loeb, Anne Leonard
  - Loeb, Jacques, 4 folders
    Includes: Letters to SF on research into problems of heterogeneous hybridization, 1914. Letters on work of Gelarie at Pacific Grove, 1914. Request to SF for funds to bring Otto Warburg to Pacific Grove, 1915. Correspondence about various European scientists and the possibilities of their coming to U. S. during WWI. Correspondence on work of Uhlenhuth under Loeb at Pacific Grove. Letter to SF explaining need for a journal of physiochemical biology, 4/18/18. Letter to SF about a discussion with T. H. Morgan and the founding of the Journal of General Physiology. (Loeb argued that the publication of high-caliber journals in this country would relieve future generations of dependence on German scientists and scientific institutions.), 5/16/18. General correspondence of Journal of General Physiology. Letters to SF on work of Samuel Meltzer, 4/24/19; of Selig Hecht, 2/7/21, 2/1/24; on visit of L. Michaelis to U. S., 1924.